Dorothy Kenyon Papers, 1850-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
Untitled speech ["poverty is the last failure of democracy..."] delivered on unidentified occasion n.d. Box 23
Tributes and introductions
"The Man I Admire Most," speech for unidentified occasion 6/47 Box 20
Untitled remarks about Florence Allen from NYU School of Law dinner in honor of Florence Allen 11/48 Box 21
"Carlo Tresca," notes for speech delivered at Tresca Memorial Committee meeting 1/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about Nellie Swartz ["My first meeting with Nellie--saffron yellow tweed suit..."] delivered at Nellie Swartz's dinner 3/51 Box 21
Untitled notes for remarks at the 70th birthday of Walter Frank 2/52 Box 21
"Howard Lindsay Introduction," remarks for ADA Roosevelt Day Dinner 2/55 Box 22
Untitled remarks introducing Eleanor Roosevelt at Cooperative Institute 7/55 Box 22
Untitled remarks introducing Herbert Lehman at ADA's 9th Annual Roosevelt Day Dinner 2/56 Box 22
Untitled remarks to introduce Eleanor Roosevelt to Cooperative Institute at Bard College 7/56 Box 22
Untitled remarks to introduce Eleanor Roosevelt to Cooperative Institute at Bard College 7/58 Box 22
"In Memorium--Seymour Bernhard 1959 Box 22
Tribute to Evelyn Preston Baldwin by DK at Baldwin's memorial service in NYC 6/62 Box 22
Untitled remarks introducing Herbert Lehman at ADA's 9th Annual Roosevelt Day Dinner 2/56 Box 22
Untitled remarks to introduce Eleanor Roosevelt to Cooperative Institute at Bard College 7/56 Box 22
Untitled remarks to introduce Eleanor Roosevelt to Cooperative Institute at Bard College 7/58 Box 22
Tribute to Evelyn Preston Baldwin by DK at Baldwin's memorial service in NYC 6/62 Box 22
"Eleanor Roosevelt," delivered to Hudson Guild Club Navy Scouts 11/62 Box 22
Untitled tribute to John F. Kennedy delivered at forum called by Workmen's Circle 11/63 Box 23
Untitled tribute to Bill Harlow delivered at Chelsea New Democratic Club (?) 1/64 Box 23
"Norman Dorsen," remarks delivered at League for Mutual Aid 3/71 Box 23
Introduction of Ramsey Clark delivered at Women's City Club 3/71 Box 23
United Nations and internationalism
"United Nations Commission on the Status of Women" 9/44 Box 20
"San Francisco and After," speech for Council of Jewish Women, Toronto Canada 5/45 Box 20
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast about Commission on the Status of Women 3/47 Box 20
"The Status of Women Under the U.N.," speech at International Women's Day Celebration of Pioneer Women's Organization 3/47 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech on UN and Human rights for Young Buddhists Association 5/47 Box 20
"The United Nations Commission on Status of Women 1947 Box 20
"A Constructive Philosophy for Our Time" 7/47 Box 20
"Duties of Citizenship," speech for Alpha Omricon Pi in Roanoke, VA 7/47 Box 20
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast, "The World Front" 7/47 Box 20
"Women and the United Nations," for Colby College Forum on "Today's World Through Women's Eyes" 7-8/47 Box 20
"United Nations, Freedom of Information," notes for speech before International Council of Women 9/47 Box 20
"Woman's Eye View [of the UN"], notes for speech for Woman's Action Committee 10/47 Box 20
"Can the United Nations Preserve the Peace?" speech at Norwalk 9/47 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Women's Eye View--Visit to UN with Florence Allen"] for College Women's Club of Montclair] 10/47 Box 20
Notes on "Women's Eye View Speech" for League of Women Voters of Bronxville: manuscript 10/47 Box 20
"Woman's Eye View of UN," speech at Harrisburg 11/47 Box 20
"Woman's Eye View" notes for speech in Hackensack 11/47 Box 20
"A Plea for the United Nations" 11/47 Box 20
"United Nations Commission on the Status of Women" 11/47 Box 20
Untitled speech ["blue-print machinery..."] on UN for Phi Beta Kappa Alumnae 12/47 Box 20
"Larger view" speech for Riverdale 12/47 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Why Freedom Train eliminates time and space"] about UN in Miami, FL 12/47 Box 20
"Women and the United Nations" 1947 Box 20
"Citizenship and the United Nations 1947 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Thank you, very much. I am sure you will al be very happy to hear that I am not going to discuss women"] given at Smith College 1947 Box 20
"Lake Success," remarks for radio broadcast 1947 Box 20
"A Plea for the United Nations," printed article from The Survey Jan/Feb/Mar 1948 Box 21
"We and the United Nations" 3/48 Box 21
Untitled remarks [It is a familiar slip of the tongue to say United States when one means United Nations] from panel discussion "Shifting Status of Women" at Women's Bureau Conference 2/48 Box 21
"Women and the United Nations," notes for speech for American Association of University Women, Poughkeepsie 3/48 Box 21
"Cooperation and World Order," remarks for radio broadcast 3/48 Box 21
"Women in the United Nations" 3/48 Box 21
"Women and the World," notes for speech in Cincinnati 4/48 Box 21
"The Responsibility of Citizens for the U.N. 4/48 Box 21
"Women and the United Nations," speech given before Soroptimists Club of Detroit 4/48 Box 21
"The Responsibility of American Women," speech before Pennsylvania Federation of Women's Clubs Convention 5/48 Box 21
"Women's Problems as Reviewed by the U.N.," speech before Massachusetts Division of the American Association of University Women" 5/48 Box 21
"The United Nations 6/48 Box 21
Untitled speech ["I can remember nothing of my high school speaker. Some old man. Now I am he."] about U.N. at Congers Grammar School graduation exercises 6/48 Box 21
"Women and the UN 7/48 Box 21
"Some Problems in the Field of Nationality of Married Women," speech delivered before the International Bar Association meeting 7/48 Box 21
"The United Nations 8/48 Box 21
"Commission on the Status of Women Broadcast," remarks for radio broadcast 9/48 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN delivered at Lebanon, PA 9/48 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN delivered to Stamford Junior League 10/48 Box 21
"The Challenge to Women in World Affairs," speech delivered at Zonta District III Conference 10/48 Box 21
"The Place of Women in the UN 5-6/48 Box 21
"The Commission on the Status of Women 1948 Box 21
"The United Nations 11/48 Box 21
Notes for untitled speech about UN delivered in Milwaukee 11/48 Box 21
Untitled remarks about UN ["we are in an era of great change"] delivered at Cooperative League meeting in Minnesota 11/48 Box 21
"Women and the United Nations," excerpts from address before Real Estate Board 11/48 Box 21
"US in UN," speech delivered to public school teachers for the American Association of the United Nations 12/48 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN delivered to Protestant Council 1/49 Box 21
Notes for untitled speech delivered in New Britain, CT 2/49 Box 21
"Toward an International Bill of Rights," speech delivered to Ethical Culture Society of Brooklyn 2/49 Box 21
"Equality and Freedom 3/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN [Commission set up of UN "federated freedoms"] delivered at American Junior College in Beirut, Lebanon 3/49 Box 21
Untitled press release about Regional Conference of Women meeting in Beirut 4/49 Box 21
"East and West Meet 5/49 Box 21
Untitled statement about UN Commission on the Status of Women meetings in Beirut 5/49 Box 21
Notes for untitled remarks ["Introduce my gang"] given as UN Delagate before National Women's Organizations Commission on the Status of Women 5/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN ["There are days in life that one remembers and this is one of them"] delivered at Commencement exercises at Beaver College 6/49 Box 21
Notes for untitled speech about UN Commission on the Status of Women ["Margaret Hickey, Purpose of our commission"], delivered before National Board of Federation of Business and Professional Women 7/49 Box 21
"Fundamental Freedoms for All," draft of article about UN Commission on the Status of Women for Women's Press 7/49 Box 21
"Women and the United Nations," notes for speech at Chautauqua 8/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN women's commission ["Fundamental freedoms part of human rights..."] delivered at Church Women's Council 9/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about UN women's commission ["Charter--fundamental freedoms"] delivered at Lycoming College 10/49 Box 21
"Women's Place in the UN," speech delivered at Women's Forum, Richmond, VA 11/49 Box 21
"East and West Meet," notes for speech to Westfield Women's Club 11/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about international organizations ["Days in life to remember--I remember when..."] given at unidentified occasion 1949 Box 21
Untitled speech about internationalism ["Terrifying but thrilling--trail-blazing, spell of frontier..."] 1949 Box 21
"Duties of Citizenship," speech delivered to Omricon Pi 7/49 Box 21
"Crossing New Frontiers 1/50 Box 21
Untitled speech on UN women's commission ["Peace, freedom, fundamental freedoms..."] delivered to Women's University Club 1/50 Box 21
"Human Rights and Women's Too," speech delivered to Young People's American ORT 1/50 Box 21
"Beirut: East and West Women Meet 1950 Box 21
"East Meets West," speech delivered to National Secretaries' Association in Newark, NJ 1/50 Box 21
"Human Rights," speech delivered to New Era Club 2/50 Box 21
Untitled speech ["New frontiers worldwide"] about UN, delivered at unidentified occasion in Youngstown, OH 3/50 Box 21
Untitled speech ["human rights taken for granted till Hitler came..."] about UN women's commission delivered to Women's Division of Jewish Labor Committee 3/50 Box 21
"Human Rights," speech delivered before Phi Beta Kappa Association, Richmond, VA 1950 Box 21
Untitled speech ["Great renaissance in human rights..."] delivered at Kansas State College 4/50 Box 21
"Human Rights," notes for speech delivered to New York Americans for Democratic Action 4/50 Box 21
"Human Rights in the World and at Home," speech delivered at Democratic Luncheon, Madison, WI 6/50 Box 21
"Through World Community 6/50 Box 21
"The UN and You," speech delivered to National Council of Jewish Women-Newark and Civic Club of Bridgeton 10/50 Box 21
Untitled speech about U.N. ["Difficult to know what to think--pattern of a month ago..."] delivered at Pembroke College 12/50 Box 21
"United Nations on Trial," speech delivered to The Group 1/51 Box 21
"You and the UN," excerpts from speech delivered at Central Presbyterian Church 1/51 Box 21
"The UN and the Citizen," speech delivered at Swarthmore College 3/51 Box 21
"The UN and Iowa," speech delivered at Coe Cornell College and Phi Beta Kappa in Cedar Rapids, IA 3/51 Box 21
"Women's Freedom in Our New World," notes for speech delivered at Providence YWCA 4/51 Box 21
"Beirut--East and West Women Meet 4/51 Box 21
"Women in World Affairs," speech delivered at unidentified occasion 5/51 Box 21
"UN and Us," speech delivered at Babylon UN Day Celebration 10/51 Box 21
"The Bill of Human Rights," speech delivered at Ridgewood, NJ, American Association for the United Nations 2/52 Box 21
"Our Responsibilities as a World Power," speech at Honors Convocation at Carleton College 5/52 Box 21
Untitled speech ["Beginnings of UN--Human rights, peace not enough..."] delivered to Newtown League of Women Voters 12/52 Box 21
"The UN in Danger," speech delivered to American Association of University Women at Wilson College 4/53 Box 21
"A Lawyer Looks at the Middle East," speech delivered to American Friends of the Middle East 4/53 Box 21
"The Bricker Amendment--A Reactionary Proposal" 5/53 Box 21
Untitled introduction of Madame Paudit delivered at Women in World Affairs luncheon 11/53 Box 21
"Bricker Amendment," speech delivered at Americans for Democratic Action-Asbury Park 1/54 Box 22
"UN--Success or Failure?" speech delivered to New Era Club 1/54 Box 22
"Bricker," speech delivered to East Side Americans for Democratic Action 2/54 Box 22
"The UN and Human Rights," speech delivered to Poughkeepsie American Association of University Women 3/54 Box 22
"The World We Live In--The UN and Us," speech delivered at Prospect Heights Girls High School 6/54 Box 22
Untitled remarks about UN ["Ad hoc commission on discrimination in South Africa..."] delivered on unidentified occasion circa 1954 Box 22
"Women's Commission," notes for speech delivered at unidentified occasion circa 1954 Box 22
"UN(?) National Platform," notes for speech delivered at Bronx ADA 2/55 Box 22
"UN the Next Ten Years," speech delivered at ADA Workshop at Bard College 8/55 Box 22
Untitled speech ["Talking about UN--How can we understand..."] delivered to Phi Beta Kappa chapter of Lehigh University 11/55 Box 22
"The U.N.--a Woman's Eye View of the Middle East," speech delivered to Religious Society of Friends 12/55 Box 22
"Human Rights--After Ten Years," speech delivered to Teachers' Guild Conference 11/58 Box 22
"Human Rights," speech delivered before Bronx chapter of AAUW 12/59 Box 22
"What Are Problems of the UN?" speech delivered to Ridgewood NJ branch of AAUW and Ethical Culture Society 10/60 Box 22
"A Quiet Backwater at the UN," speech delivered to Madison, NJ AAUW 3/61 Box 22
"Universal Declaration of Human Rights," by DK and Lula E. Bachman n.d. Box 23
Women's status and women's rights
"Community Property 5/25 Box 18
"Community Property (revised)" 7/26 Box 18
"The Family," 8/26 Box 18
Rights of Personality 12/26 Box 18
"Has your Husband Made a Will?" by Grace Turner according to an Approved Interview with Dorothy Kenyon 1/27 Box 18
"Marriage and Divorce" 2/29 Box 18
"The Household" 2/29 Box 18
"Our New Inheritance Law 12/29 Box 18
Nullification or Repeal 10/30 Box 18
"Extracts from a Speech by Dorothy Kenyon at the Annual Convention of the NY State League of Women Voters, 11/30 11/30 Box 18
Black Eyes 1931 Box 18
"Women, Infants and Lunatics" 2/31 Box 18
The Independent Woman 11/31 Box 18
"Medieval or Modern--Which?" 11/33 Box 18
A Married Woman Makes a Will 4/34 Box 18
Some Economic Aspects of the Mayor's Plan Affecting Married Women 1934 Box 18
Petition to the Congress on Behalf of Certain Married Women Formerly Employed in the New York City Post Office 2/34 Box 18
Equal Rights 5/35 Box 18
Brief Submitted to the Judicial Council by this New York League of Women Voters on Behalf of Jury Service for Women on the Same Terms as Men 1935 Box 18
Women Jurors--Why Not? 2/35 Box 18
"Press Release" for National League of Women Voters 4/35 Box 18
Women in Our Changing Political Economy 6/35 Box 18
Discrimination Against Women 11/35 Box 18
"Speeches Used at Debate on Women Jurors," notes for remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 5/36 Box 19
Changing Status of Women 5/36 Box 19
"Do Present Trends Imply Future Limitations 6/37 Box 19
"Next Steps in the Emancipation of Women 2/36 Box 19
Women and Government 4/36 Box 19
The Position of Women 12/36 Box 19
"The Pros and Cons of the Equal Rights Amendment," transcript of radio broadcast 3/37 Box 19
"Specific Bills for Specific Ills is the Only Answer," for Independent Woman 4/37 Box 19
Unidentified draft about women and government 1937 Box 19
Notes about Italian women and fascism 1937 Box 19
"The Woman's Charter 7/37 Box 19
"To End Discriminations Against Women: Specific Bills" in Independent Woman 5/37 Box 19
"Opinion as to the Legal Effect of the Action Taken at the 1937 Convention of the National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs Approving the Equal Rights Amendment" 1937 Box 19
"Women's Unique Contribution" 11/26 Box 18
"Women in Politics," remarks for radio broadcast 12/37 Box 19
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast, ["Women jurors..."] 12/37 Box 19
"Jury Duty--What it Means" 2/38 Box 19
Untitled notes for speech ["Magna Carta..."] 3/38 Box 19
"Women in the Professions 3/38 Box 19
"Women Enter a New World" 6/38 Box 19
"The League of Nations and the Legal Status of Women 7/38 Box 19
Untitled congratulatory remarks to women of American Labor Party 11/38 Box 19
"The Threat to Women in the New European Alignment and What Geneva is Doing to Help," remarks to New York Business and Professional Women 11/38 Box 19
"Can Girls Be Lawyers 3/39 Box 19
Untitled speech to American Women's Club in London 1/39 Box 19
"Liberalizing Our Divorce Laws," for forum at NYU 4/39 Box 19
"Opening Doors," remarks at Phi Beta Kappa 5/39 Box 19
"Married Women and Jobs," notes for speech to Business and Professional Women 5/39 Box 19
"Women Advancing," speech at Keuka College 6/39 Box 19
"How Women Have Achieved as Citizens," speech at AAUW Convention 6/39 Box 19
"Discussion at Democratic Regional Conference The Attack Upon Married Women's Jobs," summary of DK's remarks 6/39 Box 19
"Women's Influence in Economic Justice," speech at Williamstown Institute of Human Relations 8/39 Box 19
"Women and Economic Justice 11/39 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks to Women's Democratic Club 12/39 Box 19
"Women in the Law," radio broadcast sponsored by the U.S. Office of Education and the Federal Security Agency 12/39 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks about the history of women's rights movement for Brooklyn Smith Club 1/40 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks to American Women Bankers 1/40 Box 19
"The Status of Women," speech to Zonta Club 1/40 Box 19
"Should Married Women Work," speech to Connecticut College Club 2/40 Box 19
"NJ Status of Women," notes for speech to NJ AAUW 2/40 Box 19
"The World is Our Home," speech at University of Kentucky 2/40 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks re 2/40 Box 19
Untitled notes re 3/40 Box 19
"Women's Participation," notes for remarks to American Labor Party 3/40 Box 19
"A Citizen's Responsibility in a Democracy," speech to Business and Professional Women 4/40 Box 19
Untitled remarks to ALP 8/40 Box 19
"European Women Under Fascism," speech for Woman's Centennial Congress 11/40 Box 19
Untitled speech ["Mistress Margaret Brent"] for Baltimore Phi Beta Kappa 2/41 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Democracy--Where do women come in?"] for American Jewish Congress 2/41 Box 20
"Woman's World of the Future," notes for speech at Goucher College 4/41 Box 20
"Why I am an Enemy of Nazism" 6/41 Box 20
"Position of Working Women in a Democracy," speech at Hunter College 6/41 Box 20
"Alma Kitchell's Streamline Journal," remarks for radio broadcast 7/41 Box 20
Untitled notes ["Installation--Cora Davis"] for remarks at Soroptimists conference 8/42 Box 20
"Legal Status of Women," notes for speech in Atlantic City 3/42 Box 20
Statement by DK representing AAUW before House Ways and Means Committee re 3/42 Box 20
"Memorandum in Opposition to Proposal to Require Compulsory Joint Income Tax Returns of Husbands and Wives," submitted to House Ways and Means Committee 3/42 Box 20
"Women in the War and After," speech for the Council of Women 4/42 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Amy Lowell Says war is a pattern..."] for Sweet Briar College 4/42 Box 20
"National Needs and Resources," in The Institute in Review 4/42 Box 20
Untitled article ["Most of the states have by now achieved substantial equality..."] for Christian Science Monitor 4/42 Box 20
"Women and the World Order," speech given at Smith College 6/42 Box 20
Untitled speech "Washington was probably right when he warned us in 1789 against entangling alliances..."] 1789 Box 23
Untitled radio broadcast for People's Platform, ["How should we deal with enemy aliens?"] 7/42 Box 20
"Ease of Entering Professions," radio broadcast 11/42 Box 20
"Equal Pay for Equal Work 11/42 Box 20
"Are the Women of American Working Full-out for Victory Yet?" radio broadcast 11/42 Box 20
"Women Doctors in the Army 12/42 Box 20
Untitled speech for Women in War Congress at Girls Commercial High School 12/42 Box 20
"England Leads the Way," speech for Women's City Club 2/43 Box 20
"What's Wrong with Women Doctors?" speech for Cosmopolitan Club 2/43 Box 20
"Women in the Post-War World," speech at Fifth Avenue Forum 2/43 Box 20
"Women as a Force in Legislation," notes for speech for National Jewish Council 2/43 Box 20
Untitled notes ["Shifting times--may shift for women too"] for speech 4/43 Box 20
"The Fifth Freedom 4/43 Box 20
Untitled notes ["War's break down barriers--truism now"] for speech in Canada 4/43 Box 20
"Compulsory Registration of Women 4/43 Box 20
"World After the War," notes for speech at Women's City Club of NY 5/43 Box 20
Untitled notes ["Tide.. ."] for remarks at Annual Board Meeting of American Medical Women's Association 6/43 Box 20
"Woman's Place in the Post-War World," radio broadcast including DK for League of Women Voters 6/43 Box 20
"Why I am Opposed to the Equal Rights Amendment 6/43 Box 20
Untitled radio broadcast for "Claire Wilson Reports 7/43 Box 20
"The Fifth Freedom 8/43 Box 20
"Should Women be Drafted?" in The American Forum of the Air 10/43 Box 20
"Women's Post War Economic Role," speech at NYU 10/43 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Room for the Judge"] in Scranton, PA 10/43 Box 20
"Women's Action Committee for Victory and Lasting Peace," remarks at NYT Conference 10/43 Box 20
Untitled remarks ["Terrible day to talk about anything..."] about women and politics 11/43 Box 20
"Post War World," speech at Credit Unions Women's Association dinner 12/43 Box 20
"Replacement of Men by Women and Equal Pay," for the Industrial Bulletin 1/44 Box 20
Untitled speech ["War does strange things..."] at Labor Standards Conference 2/44 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Advertisement--she's so nice to come home to at night..."] for speech at Buffalo YWCA 3/44 Box 20
"Is It a Man's World?" speech at Nassau County Women's Clubs Forum 4/44 Box 20
"The Equal Rights Amendment 4/44 Box 20
"Puzzled by Women," speech at Doctor's Club 9/44 Box 20
"Looking Forward," introductory remarks by CK at Annual Meeting of Women's Action Committee for Victory and Lasting Peace 5/44 Box 20
Untitled speech ["They were statesmen who started the ORT..."] at Women's American ORT 5/44 Box 20
"United Nations Commission on the Status of Women 9/44 Box 20
"The Women's Part in the Post-War World," speech at Doctor's Club of Brooklyn 10/44 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Shakespeare's sister, as Virginia Wolfe [sic] describes her..."] to NY Smith Club 3/45 Box 20
Untitled speech ["League of Nations provision--equal chance..."] given at vocational conference at New Utrecht High School 6/45 Box 20
"Carrie Chapman Catt," speech for League for Political Education 1/46 Box 20
"The Suffrage Victory," speech for celebration of Carrie Chapman Catt's birthday 1/46 Box 20
"Responsibilities of Women," speech for Queens County Women's Bar Association 5/46 Box 20
Untitled speech for International Alliance of Women Conference 8/46 Box 20
"The Chances of Women Today in Getting a Job 6/46 Box 20
"The Place of Women," lecture for Smith Alumnae College 6/46 Box 20
"Is the Equal Rights Amendment Equitable to Women?" speech for CBS 7/46 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech ["International Alliance--what it is..."] for Soroptimists 10/46 Box 20
"Sisterhood of Jewish Women 10/46 Box 20
"Political Responsibilities," speech give at Cedarhurst, Long Island 10/46 Box 20
"One World, One People," speech in favor of Commission of the Status of Women at one day workshop on the United Nations sponsored by Operation Cooperation 12/46 Box 20
"Alimony," draft of article for The Woman 1946 Box 20
"Victories Won 3/47 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Economic and Social Council has approved our program..."] for Pioneer Women's Organization 3/47 Box 20
Untitled remarks for question and answer session ["Well the Russians have had a good joke at the expense of all of us..."] at WMCA 3/47 Box 20
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast about Commission on the Status of Women 3/47 Box 20
Untitled speech ["The war showed what women, aided by the machine, could do"] for unidentified occasion 4/47 Box 20
"The Status of Women Under the U.N.," speech at International Women's Day Celebration of Pioneer Women's Organization 3/47 Box 20
"American Woman's Association 5/47 Box 20
"Women are Human Beings:" typescript 5/47 Box 20
"Victories on the International Front 5/47 Box 20
"Women and the United Nations," for Colby College Forum on "Today's World Through Women's Eyes" 7-8/47 Box 20